Guide to the Cornell and Ithaca concert and event programs, 1886-1990
Cornell and Ithaca concert and event programs
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell and Ithaca concert and event programs, 1886-1990.
37-7-3854
.5 cubic feet.
Printed Materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes general concerts at Ithaca High School and Cornell University.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes general concerts at Ithaca High School and Cornell University, 1943-1971; Bailey Hall and Statler concert series, 1907-1986; Sage Chapel Choir, 1945-1972; miscellaneous events at Cornell and Ithaca College, 1926-1989, including theater, Gilbert and Sullivan operettas, dance, and ice skating; community events, including the Civic Opera and Ithaca High School concerts, 1946-1966; and Ithaca Community Players, 1925-1959 and 1978-1990. Also "Concerts at Cornell," 1933-1934 and 1934-1935. Programs from Wilgus Opera House for the Ithaca Quartet, 1886 and Cornell Banjo and Guitar Club, 1890.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Ithaca Civic Opera.; Ithaca College.; Ithaca Community Players.; Ithaca High School.; Sage Chapel Choir.
Subjects:
Concert programs--New York State--Ithaca.; Music--Societies, etc.
Form and Genre Terms:
Programs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Concert Services (paid), Location: Bailey Hall, Statler Hotel, Willard Straight Theatre, 1907-1947 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Concert Services (paid), Location: Bailey Hall, Statler Hotel, Willard Straight Theatre, 1948-1952 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Concert Services (paid), Location: Bailey Hall, Statler Hotel, Willard Straight Theatre, 1953-1960 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Concert Services (paid), Location: Bailey Hall, Statler Hotel, Willard Straight Theatre, 1961-1964 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Concert Services (paid), Location: Bailey Hall, Statler Hotel, Willard Straight Theatre, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Concert Services (paid), Location: Bailey Hall, Statler Hotel, Willard Straight Theatre, 1969-1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- General Concerts, Location: Cornell University, Time: Sunday and Monday afternoons/p.m., 1943-1957 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- General Concerts, Location: Cornell University, Time: Sunday and Monday afternoons/p.m., 1958-1966 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- General Concerts, Location: Cornell University, Time: Sunday and Monday afternoons/p.m., 1963-1969 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- General Concerts, Location: Cornell University, Time: Sunday and Monday afternoons/p.m., 1967-1981 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Location: Sage Chapel, 1945-1972 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Location: Cornell Theatres, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Cornell University Music Events: Drama, Gilbert, Sullivan, Dance Club, Ice Skating, etc., 1926-1962 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Cornell University Music Events: Drama, Gilbert, Sullivan, Dance Club, Ice Skating, etc., 1963-1989 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Community Events: Civic Opera, High School, 1946-1966 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Community Events, Community Players, 1925-1959 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Community Events, Community Players, 1978-1990 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Concerts at Cornell, 1925-1990 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Ithaca Musical Events, 1886, 1890, 1976-1988 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  Includes programs for Wilgus Opera House for the Ithaca Quartet, 1886 and Cornell Banjo and Guitar Club, 1890.